<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--################################################################################-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### Copyright (c) 2012 Roger Grantham                                        ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### All rights reserved.                                                     ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### This file is part of Verba-Android.                                      ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### Verba-Android is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify    ###-->
<!--### it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by     ###-->
<!--### the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or        ###-->
<!--### (at your option) any later version.                                      ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### Verba-Android is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,         ###-->
<!--### but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of           ###-->
<!--### MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the            ###-->
<!--### GNU General Public License for more details.                             ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--### You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License        ###-->
<!--### along with Verba-Android.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.   ###-->
<!--###                                                                          ###-->
<!--################################################################################-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VERBA</string>
    <string name="searchBox">quod uerbum vīs discere?</string>
    <string name="search">mē docē</string>
    <string name="clear">dele tabellam</string>
    <string name="resourceNotFound">mē paenitet, nam nūllum inuentum est.</string>
    <string name="progressTitle">Completing installation...</string>
    <string name="progressMessage">Please wait while the dictionary is made ready for first use.</string>
    <string name="progressCompletingMessage">Finishing up...</string>
    <string name="insufficientStorageMessage">Insufficient storage for dictionary: required %1$d bytes, but found only %2$d bytes</string>
    <string name="about_label">About</string>
    <string name="about">
        This little application is greatly indebted to the free/libre software and data contributed by the Perseus project.\n
        I wrote this app to satisfy a personal need, but I hope that verba-android can be of use to others.\n
        This is beta-quality software; please report issues and feature requests here: \n
        https://github.com/grantham/verba-android/issues\n\n
        <em>Hacking is <strong>strongly encouraged</strong></em>:\n
        Source is available from https://github.com/grantham/verba-android. Hack away!
    </string>

    <string name="contribute_label">Hack</string>
    <string name="contribute">
       Hack away! Source is available from https://github.com/grantham/verba-android \n
       Planned features for later releases:\n
        * Keep a list of words looked up five or more times to be exported as flash cards\n
        * Reduce storage requirements while still providing off-line use\n
        * Provide a service for other applications to use for part-of-speech tagging and general word lookup\n
        * Other ideas suggested by users and hackers.
    </string>
    <string name="about_licensing_label">Licensing</string>
    <string name="about_licensing">
Verba-Android is released under the GPL v3 license and is based on the database produced by the Verba-Console project (see http://www.magnopere.org/index.html#verba-console)\n
\n
The underlying data in this database comes from two sources:\n
\n
1. An Elementary Latin Dictionary (1895) by Charlton T. Lewis (see http://www.archive.org/details/anelementarylat01lewigoog).  This work is in the public domain, but was encoded into TEI by the Tufts University Perseus Project (http://www.perseus.tufts.edu) and the TEI-encoded XML file is released under the Creative Commons ShareAlike 3.0 License (http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/us/). I understand the copyright claim can only pertain to the XML encoding the project provided and cannot extend to the underlying work which is already in the public domain.\n
\n
2. A Latin morphology file produced by the Perseus Project (http://www.perseus.tufts.edu), and and which (as far as I can tell) is licensed under Mozilla Public License 1.1 (MPL 1.1) (see http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/MPL-1.1.html)\n
\n
Because of its use of the above-mentioned morphology file, the verba-console app is licensed under the Mozilla Public License 1.1 (MPL 1.1) with the option to also license under the GPL. Note that Verba-Android does not use either of the above-mentioned Perseus project files, but rather depends on the output of a program which is licensed in a compatible way to the sources it uses.\n
\n
Copyright (c) 2012 Roger Grantham\n
\n
All rights reserved.\n
\n
Verba-Android is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.\n
\n
Verba-Android is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License for more details.\n
\n
You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with Verba-Android.  If not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/\n
    </string>
    <string name="gpl_label">GPL</string>
    <string name="gpl">
        GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE
        Version 3, 29 June 2007
        See http://www.gnu.org/licenses/
    </string>
</resources>
